Register of the Commission for Relief in Belgium Records, 1914-1930
Hoover Institution Archives
- NEW YORK OFFICE PERSONNEL FILES, 1914-1919
  - Individual member files. Correspondence and biographical data, 1914-1919
    - Bain, H. Foster, 1918 (Folder 3)
    - Barrows, David P., 1915-1917 (Folder 4)
    - Barry, Griffin R., 1916-1918 (Folder 5)
    - Bates, Lindon W., 1918 (Folder 6)
    - Belrose, Louis, 1915-1918 (Folder 7)
    - Bertron, S. Reading, n.d. (Folder 8)
    - Bowden, Carlton G., 1916-1918 (Folder 9)
    - Brackett, Frank P., 1916-1918 (Folder 10)
    - Bradford, Henry Percy, 1916 (Folder 11)
    - Branscomb, Bennett H., 1918 (Folder 12)
    - Brodrick, Carlton T., 1918 (Folder 13)
    - Brown, Milton M., 1915-1918 (Folder 14)
    - Brown, Walter Lyman, 1917 (Folder 15)
    - Bryant, Floyd S., 1917-1918 (Folder 16)
    - Carmichael, Oliver C., 1917-1918 (Folder 17)
    - Carstairs, Charles H., 1917 (Folder 18)
    - Chadbourn, Philip H. and William H., 1915-1917 (Folder 19)
    - Chasseaud, H. Gordon, 1915-1918 (Folder 20)
    - Chatfield, Frederick H.
      - 1915-1916 (Folder 21)
      - 1917-1918 (Folder 22)
    - Chew, Oswald, 1916-1918 (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Clark, A. W., 1915-1917 (Folder 2)
    - Clarke, Archibald D. and R. Stanley, 1916-1918 (Folder 3)
    - Clason, Charles R., 1918 (Folder 4)
    - Connett, A. N., 1915-1917 (Folder 5)
    - Croll, Morris W., 1915-1918 (Folder 6)
    - Crosby, Oscar T., 1915-1917 (Folder 7)
    - Curtis, Edward D., 1915-1917 (Folder 8)
    - Cutler, Henry F., 1916-1917 (Folder 9)
    - Dana, Paul, 1917-1918 (Folder 10)
    - Dangerfield, James, Jr., 1915-1918 (Folder 11)
    - Dawson, Thomas B., 1915-1918 (Folder 12)
    - De Gruchy, Oliver W., 1916-1918 (Folder 13)
    - Dickson, J. W., 1917 (Folder 14)
    - Dunn, Harry L., 1916-1918 (Folder 15)
    - Dunn, William McKee, 1915-1918 (Folder 16)
    - Dutton, Robert M., 1915-1918 (Folder 17)
    - Dyer, Richard T., 1916-1918 (Folder 18)
    - Eckstein, Frederick, 1915-1918 (Folder 19)
    - Fleming, John H., 1918 (Folder 20)
    - Fletcher, Alfred C. B., 1915-1917 (Folder 21)
    - Fletcher, Horace, 1915-1918 (Folder 22)
    - Flint, William W., Jr., 1918 (Folder 23)
    - Gade, John A., 1916-1918 (Folder 24)
    - Gailor, Frank H., 1918 (Folder 25)
    - Galpin, Perrin C., 1915-1918 (Folder 26)
    - Gay, George I., 1916-1918 (Folder 27)
    - Gibson, Carleton B., 1914-1917 (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Gibson, Hugh, 1918 (Folder 2)
    - Glenn, J. L., Jr., 1916-1918 (Folder 3)
    - Gray, Prentiss N., 1915-1917 (Folder 4)
    - Green, Joseph C., 1915-1917 (Folder 5)
    - Gregory, Donald M. and Warren, 1916-1919 (Folder 6)
    - Gunn, Dudley B., 1915-1916 (Folder 7)
    - Gwynn, William M., 1916-1918 (Folder 8)
    - Hall, Guillermo, 1915-1918 (Folder 9)
    - Hall, William Chapman, 1916-1918 (Folder 10)
    - Hamilton, Herbert F., 1915-1918 (Folder 11)
    - Harper, George McLean, 1917 (Folder 12)
    - Hawkins, Charles, 1918 (Folder 13)
    - Heineman, Dannie N., 1918 (Folder 14)
    - Holman, Emil, 1918 (Folder 15)
    - Honnold, William L., 1917 (Folder 16)
    - House, R. T., 1916-1918 (Folder 17)
    - Hulse, William, n.d. (Folder 18)
    - Humbert, Pierre, n.d. (Folder 19)
    - Hunt, Edward Eyre, 1915-1918 (Folder 20)
    - Iliff, John G., 1915-1918 (Folder 21)
    - Irwin, W. W., 1916 (Folder 22)
    - Irwin, Will, 1915-1918 (Folder 23)
    - Jackson, George S., 1915-1917 (Folder 24)
    - Jackson, Robert A., 1916-1917 (Folder 25)
    - Jackson, William B., 1916-1917 (Folder 26)
    - Johnson, Amos D., Jr., 1915-1918 (Folder 27)
    - Jones, Thomas H., 1918 (Folder 28)
    - Kellogg, Vernon L., 1915-1918 (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Kite, St. Alban, 1915 (Folder 2)
    - Kittredge, Tracy B., 1915-1919 (Folder 3)
    - Langhorne, Marshall, 1918 (Folder 4)
    - Lathrop, Charles N., 1915-1918 (Folder 5)
    - Leach, Charles N., 1916-1917 (Folder 6)
    - Liefeld, E. T., 1915-1917 (Folder 7)
    - Lowdermilk, Walter C., 1917-1918 (Folder 8)
    - Lucas, William Palmer, 1916-1918 (Folder 9)
    - Lucey, John F., 1916-1918 (Folder 10)
    - Lytle, Ridgely, Jr., 1915-1918 (Folder 11)
    - McCarter, Robert D., 1918 (Folder 12)
    - McKenzie, Alexander, 1914-1915 (Folder 13)
    - Malabre, Alfred L., 1916-1918 (Folder 14)
    - Mapes, Lester D., 1918 (Folder 15)
    - Maurice, Arthur B., 1916-1917 (Folder 16)
    - Maverick, Robert, 1916-1917 (Folder 17)
    - Meert, Frederick W., 1918 (Folder 18)
    - Morgan, Dudley S., 1916-1917 (Folder 19)
    - Nelson, David T., 1918 (Folder 20)
    - Neville, Francis D., 1916-1918 (Folder 21)
    - Oliver, Thomas E., 1915-1918 (Folder 22)
    - Osborn, Earl D., 1916-1917 (Folder 23)
    - Paradise, Scott H., 1915 (Folder 24)
    - Pate, Maurice, 1916-1918 (Folder 25)
    - Percy, William A., 1916-1918 (Folder 26)
    - Pinchot, Gifford, 1917 (Folder 27)
    - Platt, Philip S., 1916-1917 (Folder 28)
    - Poland, William Babcock, 1915-1918 (Folder 29)
    - Potter, Francis H. and Philip B. K., 1915-1917 (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - Pratt, Henry S., 1916-1918 (Folder 2)
    - Richards, Lewis, 1917 (Folder 3)
    - Richardson, Gardner, 1915-1918 (Folder 4)
    - Rickard, Edgar, 1916-1917 (Folder 5)
    - St. Amour, James A., 1916-1917 (Folder 6)
    - Seward, S. S., Jr., 1916-1918 (Folder 7)
    - Shaler, Millard K., 1918 (Folder 8)
    - Simpson, John L., 1915-1917 (Folder 9)
    - Simpson, Richard H., 1917-1918 (Folder 10)
    - Smith, Robinson, 1915-1917 (Folder 11)
    - Spaulding, George F., 1918 (Folder 12)
    - Sperry, William H., 1915-1917 (Folder 13)
    - Stacy, T. Harwood, 1916-1918 (Folder 14)
    - Stephens, F. Dorsey, 1917 (Folder 15)
    - Stevenson, William C., 1916-1917 (Folder 16)
    - Stockton, Gilchrist B., 1915-1917 (Folder 17)
    - Stone, Carlos H., 1916-1918 (Folder 18)
    - Stratton, William W., 1915-1918 (Folder 19)
    - Straus, Oscar S., 1919 (Folder 20)
    - Stubbs, G., 1916 (Folder 21)
    - Sullivan, William M., 1917-1918 (Folder 22)
    - Thurston, E. Coppée, 1915-1917 (Folder 23)
    - Thwaits, Frederick C., 1916-1919 (Folder 24)
    - Tileston, Robert, 1916-1917 (Folder 25)
    - Torrey, Clare M., 1915-1918 (Folder 26)
    - Tuck, William Hallam, 1916 (Folder 27)
    - Van Hee, Julius A., 1917 (Folder 28)
    - Van Schaick, John Brodhead, 1915-1917 (Folder 29)
    - Warren, Robert H., 1915-1918 (Folder 30)
    - Wellington, Laurence C., 1915-1917 (Folder 31)
    - White, John Beaver, 1915-1918 (Folder 32)
    - Whiting, Almon C., 1915-1918 (Folder 33)
    - Whitney, Caspar, 1915-1918 (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Wickes, Francis C., 1915-1917 (Folder 2)
    - Williams, Edgar, 1915-1919 (Folder 3)
    - Williams, Percy H., 1914-1918 (Folder 4)
    - Withington, Robert
      - 1915-1916 (Folder 5)
      - 1917-1918 (Folder 6)
    - Young, Carl A., n.d. (Folder 7)
  - Individual candidate files (candidates who did not serve in the Commission for Relief in Belgium). Correspondence and biographical data, 1914-1917
    - A. Includes Hamilton Fish Armstrong (Folder 8)
    - B-Ba (Folder 9)
    - Be-Bo (Folder 10)
    - Bra-Bri (Folder 11)
    - Bro-Bu (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - C-Cl (Folder 2)
    - Co-Cu (Folder 3)
    - D-Di (Folder 4)
    - Do-Dy. Includes John Dos Passos (Folder 5)
    - E (Folder 6)
    - F (Folder 7)
    - G-Gi (Folder 8)
    - Go-Gw (Folder 9)
    - H-Ha (Folder 10)
    - He-Hi (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Ho (Folder 2)
    - Hu (Folder 3)
    - I (Folder 4)
    - J (Folder 5)
    - K (Folder 6)
    - L. Includes Paul M. W. Linebarger (Folder 7)
    - M-Mac (Folder 8)
    - Mah-Me (Folder 9)
    - Mi-Mo (Folder 10)
    - Mu-My (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - N (Folder 2)
    - O (Folder 3)
    - P-Ph (Folder 4)
    - Pi-Pu (Folder 5)
    - Q (Folder 6)
    - R-Ri (Folder 7)
    - Ro-Ru (Folder 8)
    - S-Sc (Folder 9)
    - Se-Sh (Folder 10)
    - Si-Sn (Folder 11)
    - Sp-Sw (Folder 12)
    - T (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - V (Folder 2)
    - W-Wa (Folder 3)
    - We-Wh (Folder 4)
    - Wi-Wr. Includes Edmund Wilson (Folder 5)
    - Y (Folder 6)
- NEW YORK OFFICE PUBLIC RELATIONS FILE, 1914-1919.
  Press releases, drafts of press releases, and clippings and other working materials for press releases
  - 1914 (Box 323)
    - September-November (Folder 1)
    - December (Folder 2)
  - 1915
    - January (Folder 3)
    - February (Folder 4)
    - March (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - April (Folder 2)
    - May (Folder 3)
    - June (Folder 4)
    - July (Folder 5)
    - August (Folder 6)
    - September (Folder 7)
    - November-December (Folder 8)
  - 1916 (Folder 9)
  - 1917 (Folder 10)
  - 1918 (Folder 11)
  - 1919 (Folder 12)
  - Undated (Folder 13)
- NEW YORK OFFICE SHIPPING RECORDS, 1914-1921
  - Intra-office memoranda, exchanged within the New York office, 1918-1919 (Box 325, Folder 1)
  - Intra-agency correspondence. Correspondence between the New York Office and other offices of the Commission for Relief in Belgium, 1914-1921
    - London Office
      - 1914 (Folder 2)
      - 1915
        - January-June (Folder 3)
        - July-December (Folder 4)
      - 1916
        - January-June (Folder 5)
        - July-December (Folder 6)
      - 1917
        - January-June (Folder 7)
        - July-December (Folder 8)
      - 1918
        - January-June (Folder 9)
        - July-December (Box 326, Folder 1)
      - 1919-1921 (Folder 2)
    - Washington Office, 1918-1919 (Folder 3)
  - General correspondence, 1918-1919
    - General, 1918-1919 (Folder 4)
    - American National Red Cross, 1918-1919 (Folder 5)
    - United States. Food Administration, 1918-1919 (Folder 6)
    - United States. Shipping Board. Includes Shipping Control Committee
      - 1918 (Folder 7)
      - 1919 (Folder 8)
  - Shipping control sheets (copies of sheets prepared by London Office)
    - 1916
      - January (Folder 9)
      - February (Folder 10)
      - March (Folder 11)
      - April (Box 327, Folder 1)
      - September (Folder 2)
      - October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
      - December (Folder 5)
    - 1917
      - January (Folder 6)
      - February (Folder 7)
      - March (Folder 8)
      - April (Box 328, Folder 1)
      - May (Folder 2)
      - June (Folder 3)
      - July (Folder 4)
      - August (Folder 5)
      - September (Folder 6)
      - October (Box 329, Folder 1)
      - November (Folder 2)
      - December (Folder 3)
    - 1918
      - January (Folder 4)
      - February (Folder 5)
      - March (Folder 6)
      - April (Box 330, Folder 1)
      - May (Folder 2)
      - June (Folder 3)
      - July (Folder 4)
      - August (Folder 5)
      - October (Folder 6)
    - 1919 (Box 331)
      - May (Folder 1)
      - June (Folder 2)
  - Shipping control sheets (prepared by New York Office)
    - General (Folder 3)
      - 1918
      - 1919 (Folder 4)
    - Working materials (draft control sheets), 1918-1919 (Folder 5)
  - Individual ship worksheets, 1918-1919
    - Aila, 1918-1919 (Folder 6)
    - Alfred Hage, 1918-1919 (Folder 7)
    - Algérie, 1919 (Folder 8)
    - Anna Maersk, 1918 (Folder 9)
    - Anten, 1919 (Folder 10)
    - Anvers, 1918-1919 (Folder 11)
    - Armistice, 1919 (Folder 12)
    - Arna, 1918-1919 (Folder 13)
    - Aspen, 1918-1919 (Folder 14)
    - Baron Baeyens, 1918-1919 (Folder 15)
    - Bavaria, 1919 (Folder 16)
    - Belos, 1918-1919 (Folder 17)
    - Berlin, 1918 (Folder 18)
    - Bia, 1918-1919 (Folder 19)
    - Bjornsterne Bjornson, 1918-1919 (Folder 20)
    - Bolmen, 1918-1919 (Folder 21)
    - Boren, 1918-1919 (Folder 22)
    - Borglum, 1918-1919 (Folder 23)
    - Calabria, 1918-1919 (Folder 24)
    - Carlsholm, 1919 (Folder 25)
    - Colombier, 1918-1919 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Consul Olsson, 1918-1919 (Folder 2)
    - Danebrog, 1918-1919 (Folder 3)
    - Dicto, 1918-1919 (Folder 4)
    - Elisabeth, 1918-1919 (Folder 5)
    - Elisabeth Maersk, 1919 (Folder 6)
    - Elisabeth van Belgie, 1918-1919 (Folder 7)
    - Escaut, 1919 (Folder 8)
    - Gallia, 1919 (Folder 9)
    - Gantoise, 1918-1919 (Folder 10)
    - Generalkonsul Pallisen, 1918 (Folder 11)
    - Gloria, 1918-1919 (Folder 12)
    - Gogsjo, 1918-1919 (Folder 13)
    - Gotaland, 1919 (Folder 14)
    - Gothland, 1918-1919 (Folder 15)
    - Gouverneur de Lantsheere, 1918-1919 (Folder 16)
    - Graecia, 1918-1919 (Folder 17)
    - Harald, 1918 (Folder 18)
    - Helmer Morch, 1918-1919 (Folder 19)
    - Herm, 1918-1919 (Folder 20)
    - Hwah Yah, 1919 (Folder 21)
    - Hwah Yih, 1919 (Folder 22)
    - Immeln, 1918-1919 (Folder 23)
    - Japan, 1919 (Folder 24)
    - Jelling, 1918-1919 (Folder 25)
    - Jethou, 1918-1919 (Folder 26)
    - Knud II, 1918-1919 (Folder 27)
    - Kronprins Gustaf Adolf, 1918-1919 (Folder 28)
    - Leopold II, 1918-1919 (Folder 29)
    - Liège, 1918-1919 (Folder 30)
    - Liguria, 1918 (Folder 31)
    - Luise Nielsen, 1918-1919 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Lygnern, 1918-1919 (Folder 2)
    - Magdala, 1918-1919 (Folder 3)
    - Magunkook, 1919 (Folder 4)
    - Mathilda, 1918 (Folder 5)
    - Mercer, 1919 (Folder 6)
    - N. F. Hoffding, 1918 (Folder 7)
    - Natal, 1918-1919 (Folder 8)
    - Newa, 1918 (Folder 9)
    - Nieuw Amsterdam, 1918 (Folder 10)
    - Nijni Novgorod, 1919 (Folder 11)
    - Nippon, 1918-1919 (Folder 12)
    - Nordhavet, 1918-1919 (Folder 13)
    - Nordland, 1918-1919 (Folder 14)
    - Nyland, 1918 (Folder 15)
    - Oluf Maersk, 1919 (Folder 16)
    - Oscar Trapp, 1918-1919 (Folder 17)
    - Oshkosh, 1919 (Folder 18)
    - Osterland, 1918-1919 (Folder 19)
    - Pacific, 1918-1919 (Folder 20)
    - President Bunge, 1918-1919 (Folder 21)
    - Regulus, 1919 (Folder 22)
    - Remier, 1918-1919 (Folder 23)
    - René, 1918-1919 (Folder 24)
    - Republica Argentina, 1918-1919 (Folder 25)
    - Ribe, 1919 (Folder 26)
    - Rollo, 1918-1919 (Folder 27)
    - Roxen, 1918-1919 (Folder 28)
    - Samland, 1918-1919 (Folder 29)
    - Sandefjord, 1918-1919 (Folder 30)
    - Sark, 1919 (Folder 31)
    - Scotia, 1918-1919 (Folder 32)
    - Senta, 1918-1919 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Sigyn, 1918-1919 (Folder 2)
    - Siljan, 1918 (Folder 3)
    - Sizergh Castle, 1919 (Folder 4)
    - Skanderborg, 1918-1919 (Folder 5)
    - Skinfaxe, 1918-1919 (Folder 6)
    - Sommen, 1918-1919 (Folder 7)
    - Sonja, 1918-1919 (Folder 8)
    - Stiklestad, 1918 (Folder 9)
    - Storviken, 1918-1919 (Folder 10)
    - Strinda, 1919 (Folder 11)
    - Sygna, 1918 (Folder 12)
    - Syrie, 1918-1919 (Folder 13)
    - Talabot, 1918-1919 (Folder 14)
    - Tasmanic, 1918 (Folder 15)
    - Texas, 1919 (Folder 16)
    - Thyra, 1918-1919 (Folder 17)
    - Tiverton, 1919 (Folder 18)
    - Toften, 1918-1919 (Folder 19)
    - Trafalgar, 1918-1919 (Folder 20)
    - Tricolor, 1918-1919 (Folder 21)
    - Tungus, 1918-1919 (Folder 22)
    - Tunisie, 1918 (Folder 23)
    - Tyr, 1918-1919 (Folder 24)
    - Ubier, 1918-1919 (Folder 25)
    - Ulrik Holm, 1918-1919 (Folder 26)
    - Unden, 1918-1919 (Folder 27)
    - Uppland, 1918-1919 (Folder 28)
    - Vessman, 1919 (Folder 29)
    - Vestland, 1918 (Folder 30)
    - Vicia, 1918-1919 (Folder 31)
    - Viken, 1918-1919 (Folder 32)
    - West Gambo, 1918-1919 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Zamora, 1918-1919 (Folder 2)
    - Sailing departures (individual ship worksheets chronologically arranged by departure date), 1919 (Folder 3)
  - Safe conduct files, 1914-1918. Files relating to securing of safe conducts for relief ships from belligerent governments
    - Procedures and sample forms, 1915-1917 (Folder 4)
    - Intra-office memoranda, exchanged within the New York Office, 1914-1918 (Folder 5)
    - Intra-agency correspondence. Correspondence between the New York Office and other offices of the Commission for Relief in Belgium, 1914-1917
      - London Office, 1914-1917 (Folder 6)
      - Rotterdam Office, 1916-1917 (Folder 7)
    - General correspondence, 1914-1918
      - General, 1915-1917 (Folder 8)
      - Dodge and Sons (Law firm), 1914-1915 (Folder 9)
      - Germany. Botschaft (U.S.)
        - 1915 (Folder 10)
        - 1916-1917 (Folder 11)
      - Great Britain. Embassy (U.S.), 1915-1917 (Folder 12)
      - Netherlands. Gezantschap (U.S.), 1915-1918 (Folder 13)
      - Norton, Lilly and Company, 1914-1915 (Folder 14)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1915 (Folder 15)
      - Spain. Embajada (U.S.), 1917 (Folder 16)
      - United States. Dept. of State, 1914-1917 (Folder 17)
    - Subject file. Correspondence and memoranda, 1914-1917 (Box 336)
      - Deutsches Rotes Kreuz, 1915 (Folder 1)
      - Ports, 1914-1917
        - Baltimore (Md.), 1914-1917 (Folder 2)
        - Boston (Mass.), 1914-1915 (Folder 3)
        - Charleston (S.C.), 1915 (Folder 4)
        - Galveston (Tex.), 1916 (Folder 5)
        - New Orleans (La.), 1914-1917 (Folder 6)
        - New York (N.Y.), 1914-1916 (Folder 7)
        - Newport News (Va.), 1915 (Folder 8)
        - Norfolk (Va.), 1914-1915 (Folder 9)
        - Philadelphia (Pa.), 1914-1917 (Folder 10)
        - Port Arthur (Tex.), 1916 (Folder 11)
        - Portland (Me.), 1915-1917 (Folder 12)
        - Portland (Ore.), 1914-1915 (Folder 13)
        - San Francisco (Calif.), 1914-1915 (Folder 14)
        - Seattle (Wash.), 1914-1915 (Folder 15)
        - Tacoma (Wash.), 1914 (Folder 16)
      - United States. Dept. of the Treasury certificates. Correspondence and memoranda regarding, 1914-1915 (Folder 17)
    - Logs, 1914-1916 (Folder 18)
    - Maps of restricted shipping zone, 1917 (Folder 19)
    - Individual ship approvals. Correspondence arranged by indicated category and thereunder alphabetically by ship, 1914-1917
      - General. Correspondence other than with British or German authorities (mainly intra-agency within the Commission for Relief in Belgium), 1915-1917
        - Outbound voyages, 1915-1917
          - A-D (Folder 20)
          - E-H (Folder 21)
          - I-N (Folder 22)
          - O-R (Box 337, Folder 1)
          - S (Folder 2)
          - T-Y (Folder 3)
        - Return voyages, 1916-1917
          - A-L (Folder 4)
          - M-V (Folder 5)
      - British approvals. Correspondence with British authorities, especially the British embassy in the United States and various British consulates, 1914-1917
        - A (Folder 6)
        - B (Folder 7)
        - C (Folder 8)
        - D (Folder 9)
        - E (Box 338, Folder 1)
        - F (Folder 2)
        - G (Folder 3)
        - H (Folder 4)
        - I-K (Folder 5)
        - L (Folder 6)
        - M-N (Folder 7)
        - O (Box 339, Folder 1)
        - P-Q (Folder 2)
        - R (Folder 3)
        - S-Sn (Folder 4)
        - So-Sy (Folder 5)
        - T-U (Folder 6)
        - V-Z (Folder 7)
      - German approvals. Correspondence mainly with German authorities, especially the German embassy in the United States, German consulates, and, later, the German Interests Department of the Swiss legation in the United States, 1914-1917
        - A-Al (Folder 8)
        - An-Ay (Box 340, Folder 1)
        - B-Be (Folder 2)
        - Bi-Br (Folder 3)
        - C-Cl (Folder 4)
        - Co-Cr (Folder 5)
        - D (Folder 6)
        - E-El (Folder 7)
        - En-Eu (Folder 8)
        - F-Fi (Folder 9)
        - Fl-Fr (Box 341, Folder 1)
        - G-Go (Folder 2)
        - Gr-Gu (Folder 3)
        - H-Ha (Folder 4)
        - He-Ho (Folder 5)
        - I (Folder 6)
        - J (Folder 7)
        - K (Folder 8)
        - L-Lie (Folder 9)
        - Lin-Ly (Folder 10)
        - M (Box 342, Folder 1)
        - N (Folder 2)
        - O-Oo (Folder 3)
        - Ot-Ov (Folder 4)
        - P (Folder 5)
        - Q (Folder 6)
        - R-Re (Folder 7)
        - Ri-Ro (Folder 8)
        - S-Sal (Folder 9)
        - Sam-Sn (Box 343, Folder 1)
        - So (Folder 2)
        - St (Folder 3)
        - Sy (Folder 4)
        - T (Folder 5)
        - U-V (Folder 6)
        - W-Z (Folder 7)
  - Arrival in Rotterdam reports (Box 344)
    - 1916 (Folder 1)
    - 1917 (Folder 2)
    - 1918 (Folder 3)
  - Cargo reports, 1917-1919 (Folder 4)
  - Cash statements
    - 1918
      - August-September (Folder 5)
      - October-December (Folder 6)
    - 1919 (Folder 7)
  - Charts, 1917-1919 (Folder 8-10)
  - Contract logs, 1915-1917
    - Lard, 1915-1917 (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Milk, 1916-1917 (Folder 2)
    - Peas and beans, 1916-1917 (Folder 3)
    - Pork products, 1915-1917 (Folder 4)
    - Sugar and flour, 1915-1917 (Folder 5)
    - Wheat and barley, 1915-1917 (Folder 6)
  - Maritime miscellany reports, 1919 (Folder 7)
  - Particulars regarding steamers reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 8)
  - Purchasing reports, 1918-1919 (Folder 9)
  - Purchasing requisitions, 1918 (Folder 10)
  - Steamers landed reports, 1915-1919 (Folder 11)
  - Steamers sailed reports, 1918 (Folder 12)
  - Transportation reports, 1916-1918 (Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous shipping reports, 1917-1919 (Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous statistical data, 1917-1919 (Folder 15)
  - Subject file. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, and statistics, 1917-1919
    - Belgium. Légation (U.S.). Correspondence re, 1918 (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - Bunkers, 1918 (Folder 2)
    - Cargoes
      - 1917-1918 (Folder 3)
      - 1919 (Folder 4)
    - Charters, 1918-1919 (Folder 5)
    - Clothing campaign, 1918-1919 (Folder 6)
    - Commodity exports, 1918 (Folder 7)
    - Office furniture, 1918-1919 (Folder 8)
    - Office leases, 1918-1919 (Folder 9)
    - Purchases and donations, 1917-1918 (Folder 10)
    - Relief program (goals and performance), 1917-1919 (Folder 11)
    - Sacks, 1917 (Folder 12)
    - Submarine losses, 1918 (Folder 13)
    - Tonnage allocations, 1918-1919 (Folder 14)
- NEW YORK OFFICE WAREHOUSE RECORDS, 1914-1920
  - Correspondence, 1914-1917. Includes bills of lading (Box 347)
    - Alabama
      - Magnolia Compress and Warehouse Company (Mobile), 1915 (Folder 1)
      - Warrant Warehouse Company (Birmingham), 1915 (Folder 2)
    - Arizona. Pioneer Transfer Company (Phoenix), 1915 (Folder 3)
    - Arkansas. Terminal Warehouse Company (Little Rock), 1915 (Folder 4)
    - California
      - Haslett Warehouse Company (San Francisco), 1915-1917 (Folder 5)
      - Shattuck and Nimmo Warehouse Company (Los Angeles), 1915-1916 (Folder 6)
    - Colorado. Benedict Warehouse and Transfer Company (Denver), 1915 (Folder 7)
    - Connecticut
      - A. Brazos and Sons, Inc. (Middletown), 1915 (Folder 8)
      - Bill Brothers Company (Hartford), 1915 (Folder 9)
      - H. T. Smith Express Company (Meriden), 1915-1916 (Folder 10)
    - Delaware. Charles Warner Company (Wilmington), 1915 (Folder 11)
    - District of Columbia. Littlefield, Alvord and Company (Washington), 1915 (Folder 12)
    - Florida. Wiesenfeld Warehouse Company (Jacksonville), 1915 (Folder 13)
    - Idaho. Peasley Transfer and Storage Company (Boise), 1915 (Folder 14)
    - Illinois
      - Glynn's Fireproof Storage Company (Cairo), 1915 (Folder 15)
      - Sibley Warehouse and Storage Company (Chicago), 1915-1917 (Folder 16)
    - Indiana. Tripp Warehouse Company (Indianapolis), 1915-1916 (Folder 17)
    - Iowa
      - Calder's Van and Storage Company (Cedar Rapids), 1915-1916 (Folder 18)
      - Ewert and Richter Express and Storage Company (Davenport), 1915-1916 (Folder 19)
      - Merchants Transfer and Storage Company (Des Moines), 1915 (Folder 20)
      - Morningside Dray and Auto Company (Sioux City), 1915 (Folder 21)
    - Kansas
      - Bryan Transfer and Storage Company (Wichita), 1915 (Folder 22)
      - City Transfer and Storage Company (Hutchinson), 1915 (Folder 23)
    - Kentucky
      - Crutcher Brothers Company (Louisville), 1915-1916 (Folder 24)
      - Kelly Storage and Distributing Company (Lexington), 1915 (Folder 25)
    - Louisiana (Box 348)
      - Norton, Lilly and Company (New Orleans), 1915 (Folder 1)
      - Perilliat, Arsène (Agent: New Orleans), 1915 (Folder 2)
    - Maine (Folder 3)
      - Galt Block Warehouse Company (Portland), 1915
      - Henry McLaughlin and Company (Bangor), 1915-1916 (Folder 4)